You're probably wondering
why I asked you to come.
[PLAYFUL ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Here.
[RIBBON RUSTLING]
[GIFT OPENS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [RIBBON RUSTLING]
- [GIFT CLOSES LOUDLY]
Wait a second, what's this?
A bribe?
You think I'll forget about it
with just one gift?
I want to offer you a job.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Be my Tagalog translator
and guide.
I'll pay you 50,000 pesos
a month.
- [CASH REGISTER SFX]
- [GASPS]
Sorry, sorry.
Calm down. Calm down, self.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Sir,
you're asking me to do two jobs.
You know, two jobs.
Seventy thousand.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sixty thousand.
Take it or leave it.
Sixty-five thousand.
And I'm yours.
Kpaps?
[DING SFX]
[CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Deal.
Deal?
Deal! Yes! Deal! [THUDS]
Yes! Yes! Wooh! [CLAPS]
[SINGSONG] Sixty-five thousand!
Every month! Yes!
Yes! Wooh! Yes! [CLAPS]
Oh, I'm telling you!
You won't regret it, Kpaps!
I'll give it my all.
I'll do my absolute best!
To the point
you'll never let me go.
No, no, no, no. [CLAPS]
Yes, yes! Nice, nice!
Very good, very good! [CLAPS]
Let's get down to business.
Bring it on!
Take off your clothes.
- [SUSPENSEFUL STING]
- Huh?
Sir, what?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I said, take off your clothes.
Now.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]